#### PERSONAL STATEMENT

Young and Motivated Student, bachelor of science in Information Technology at EPITECH School.

I have many experiences in managing project. Proven success in project scopes, budgets, schedules and deliverables throughout all phases of the software development lifecycle. Combine technical and analytical aptitudes with problem-solving strengths to drive projects on time, on budget and high quality completion.

### **EDUCATION**



September 2015 - September 2016

Master - Computer & Innovation Expertise Epitech, Paris

September 2014 - June 2015

Master - IT Software development Beijing Jiaotong university, Beijing CHINA 北京交通大学

September 2010 - September 2014



Bachelor - Computer & Innovation Expertise Epitech, Lille

September 2010



Scientific Baccalaureat

Ste. Marie College , Aire sur la Lys

### LANGUAGES



### **HOBBIES**













Music

Art

## **WORK EXPERIENCES**

## September 2015 - Present



# Android Developer

PeoplBrain - Picomto, Software Editor, Lille Android Application/Librairies Development JAVA - SDK android, Git

March 2014 - August 2014



### Mobile Developer

Unitiz, Software Editor, Lille

Lead & Mobile App Development JAVA - SDK Android, JQuery Mobile, Git, Scrum

February 2013 - September 2013



### Mobile & Web Developer

Cometik, Communication Agency, Lille

Lead & Android Development Customers Formation.

JAVA - SDK Android, PHP, Agile, Software development

October 2012 - February 2013



## Back-end Developer

AdiBox. Software Editor. Lille

Web Application Development Framework Symfony 2

Juily 2011 - October 2011



### Web & mobile Application Development

Blueapps, Software Editor, Lille

Mobile App development Initiation & Drupal Experience

JAVA - SDK Android, iOS - C-Objectif, PHP Drupal

### SKILLS

Android Ruby on Rails C / C + +



